Hello and welcome
大家好 欢迎各位
As you probably know
你们也许知道了
Deep Learning has already transformed the traditional internet businesses
深度学习改变了传统互联网业务
like web search and advertising
例如如网络搜索和广告
But deep learning is also
但是深度学习同时也
enabling many new products and businesses
使得许多新产品和企业
in ways of helping people to
以很多方式帮助人们
recreate everying ranging from better healthcare
从获得更好的健康关注
where deep learning is getting really good
深度学习做的非常好的一个方面就是
at reading X-ray images
读取X光图像
to the living personalized education
到生活中的个性化教育
to precision agriculture
到精准化农业
to even self-driving cars
甚至到无人驾驶的汽车
and many others
以及其它一些方面
if you want to learn the tools of deep learning
如果你想要学习深度学习的这些工具
and be able to apply them to build these amazing things
并应用它们来做这些令人窒息的操作(X)
I want to help you get there
我将帮助你做到这一点
When you finish this sequence of courses on cousera called the specialization
当你完成cousera上面的这一系列专项课程
you'll be able to put deep learning on your resume with confidence
你就可以自信地将深度学习加到你的简历上
Over the next decade I think
在接下来的十年中 我认为
all of us have the opportunity
我们所有人都有机会
to build an amazing world and amazing society
创造一个由人工智能驱动的
that is AI-powered
美妙的世界和美妙的社会
I hope that you would play a big role
我希望你们能在创建这个由AI驱动的社会中
in the creation of this AI-powered society
扮演一个重要的角色
So that, let's get started
所以 让我们开始吧
I think that AI is the new electricity
我认为AI是新的电力
Started about 100 years ago
大约在一百年前
the electrification of our society
我们社会的电气化
transformed every major industry
改变了每个主要行业
everthing ranging from transportation
从交通运输行业
manufacturing, healthcare,
communications, and many more
到制造业 医疗保健 通讯等方面
And I think that today we see a
我认为如今我们见到了
surprisingly clear power of AI
AI明显的令人惊讶的能量
to bring about an equally big transformation
带来了同样巨大的转变
And of course, the part of AI
显然 AI的各个分支中
that is rising rapidly and driving along
发展的最为迅速的
with these developments is deep learning
就是深度学习
So today, deep learning is one of
the most highly sought-after skills
因此现在 深度学习是广受欢迎的一种技巧
in the technology world
在科技世界中
And through this course and
通过这个课程
a few courses after this one
以及这门课程后门的几门课程
I want to help you to gain
我想帮助你获取
and master those skills
并且掌握那些技能
So here's what you'll learn
下面是你将学习到的内容
in this sequence of courses
aslo called specialization on cousera
在cousera的这一系列也叫做专项课程中
In the first course
在第一门课中
you'll learn the Foundations of Neural Networks
你将学习神经网络的基础
you'll learn the Neural
Network and Deep Learning
你将学习神经网络和深度学习
This video that you are watching
is a part of this first course
你观看的这个影片是第一门课的一部分
which lasts four weeks in total
这门课将持续四周
And each of the five courses in the
specialization will be about 2 to 4 weeks
专项课程中的每门课将持续2至4周
most of them actually will
short than four weeks
大部分将少于四周
But in this first course
但是在第一门课程中
you'll learn how to build a Neural Network
您将学习如何建立神经网络
including a deep neural network
包含一个深度神经网络
and how to train them on data
以及如何在数据上面训练他们
And at the end of this course
在这门课程的结尾
you'll build a deep neural network
to recognize and guess what
你将用一个深度神经网络进行辨认
猜猜是什么？
Cats
喵星人！
For some reason
由于某种原因
there is a cat meme running around in deep learning
深度学习中会有一个猫的谜因运行
And so following tradition
所以遵循传统
in this first course we'll build a cat
第一门课我们会做一个猫的
recognizer
识别器
Then, in the second course
接下来 在第二门课中
you'll learn about the
practical aspects of Deep Learning
你将进行深度学习方面的实践
so you'll learn narrowly bulid neural network
您将学习严密地构建神经网络
how to actually get it perform well
如何真正让它表现良好
So you'll learn about
因此你将要学习
hyperparameter tuning
超参数调整
regularization
正则化
how to diagnose bias and variance
诊断偏差和方差
and advanced optimization algorithms
以及一些高级优化算法
like Momentum and Adam algorithm
比如Momentum和Adam算法
Sometimes it seems like this allow the tuning
有时候看起来这样的调整是允许的
even some black magic and
how you build in your network
有如黑魔法一样根据你建立网络的方式
So the second course which is just three weeks
所以第二门课只有三周
will demystify so that black magic
来揭开这一黑魔法的神秘面纱
In the third course, we'll just use two weeks
在第三门课中，我们将使用两周时间
to learn how to struct your machine learning project
来学习如何结构化你的机器学习工程
It turns out that
事实证明
the strategy for building a machine learning system
构建机器学习系统的策略
has change the error of deep learning
改变了深度学习的错误
So, for example
举个例子
the way you split the data
你分割数据的方式
into train, development or diff on
most called validation set
分割成训练集 比较集 或改变的验证集
and test sets
以及测试集合
has change the error of deep learning
改变了深度学习的错误
So what is the new best practice for doing that?
所以最好的实践方式是什么呢？
And what of your train set and your test set
以及你的训练集和测试集
come from different distributions
来自不同的分布
that's happening a lot more on the nueral deep learning
在深度学习中的影响很大
So how do you deal that?
那么你应该怎么处理呢？
And if you've heard of end-to-end deep learning
如果你听说过端对端深度学习
you'll also learn more about
that in this third course
你也会在第三门课中了解到更多
and see what you should use it
and maybe you shouldn't
进而了解到你是否需要使用它
The material in this third course
第三课的材料
is relatively unique
是相对比较独特的
I'm going to share with you
我将和你分享
all of the hot-one lessons we have learnt
我们了解到的所有的热门领域的
build and shaping quite of deeping learning problems
建立并且改良许多的深度学习问题
because I know
因为我知道
This is rush material that
这是当今热门的材料
is not taught in most common universities
在绝大部分大学里面不会教授的
that have deep learning courses
在他们的深度学习课堂上面
But I think it really help you
但我认为它会提供你帮助
to get the deep learning system to work well
让深度学习系统工作的更好
In the next course
在下一们课程中
we'll  then talk about
我们将会提到
Convolutional Neural Networks
卷积神经网络
often abbreviat to CNN(s)
经常缩写为 CNN（s）
Convolutional Networks or
Convolutional Neural Networks
卷积网络或者说卷积神经网络
are often apply to images
经常被用于图像领域
So you'll learn how to build this model in course 4
所以你将会在第4门课程中学到如何搭建这样的模型
Finally in course 5
最后在第5门课中
you'll learn sequence models
你将会学习到序列模型
and how to aplly them to nature language processing
以及如何将它们应用于自然语言处理
and other problems
以及其它问题
So sequence model include models like
序列模型包括的模型有
Recurrent Neural Network abbreviat to RNN
循环神经网络 简写为RNN
and LSTM models
以及LSTM模型
stands for Long Short-Term Memory models
全称是长短期记忆网络
you'll learn what this term means in course 5
你将在课程5中了解其中的时期是什么含义
and be able to aplly them to NLP problems
并且有能力应用到NLP（自然语言处理）问题
So you'll learn these models in course 5
总之你将在课程5中学习这些模型
and be able to apply them to sequence data
以及能够将它们应用于序列数据
so for example, nature language is
比如说 自然语言就是
just a sequence of words
一个单词序列
and you'll understand how this
models can be apply to
你也将能够理解这些模型如何应用到
speech recognization
语音识别
or to music generation
或者是编曲
and other problems
以及其它问题
So through these courses
因此 通过这些课程
you'll learn the tools of deep learning
你将学习深度学习的这些工具
you'll be able to apply them
你将能够去使用它们
to bulid amazing things
去做一些神奇的事情
And I hope many of you
我希望你们中的一些人
through this will also be able to advance your career
借此来提升你的职业生涯
So that
因此
let's get started
让我们一起开始
please go to the next video
请进入下一个视频
we'll talk about deep learning
aplly to supervised learning
我们将谈到深度学习在监督学习的使用